{
    "subject": "resource/Thomas_Kuhn",
    "predicate": "ontology/influencedBy",
    "object": "resource/Bertrand_Russell",
    "human_readable": "Thomas Kuhn was influenced by Bertrand Russell.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9753944873809814,
            "question": "Did Bertrand Russell have an impact on Thomas Kuhn's work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9382694959640503,
            "question": "Was Thomas Kuhn a follower of Bertrand Russell's ideas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9295417666435242,
            "question": "Were Thomas Kuhn and Bertrand Russell contemporaries?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9084312915802002,
            "question": "Who influenced Thomas Kuhn?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8874298334121704,
            "question": "What fields of study were both Thomas Kuhn and Bertrand Russell involved in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8771745562553406,
            "question": "How did Bertrand Russell's philosophy differ from Thomas Kuhn's?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8485433459281921,
            "question": "What are some of the main works by both Thomas Kuhn and Bertrand Russell?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.597126841545105,
            "question": "Can you name any other philosophers who influenced Thomas Kuhn?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5884618759155273,
            "question": "What was Bertrand Russell known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38767334818840027,
            "question": "What are some key concepts that Thomas Kuhn explored in his work?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Thomas Kuhn was influenced by Bertrand Russell.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7989_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was Bertrand Russell known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7989_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name any other philosophers who influenced Thomas Kuhn?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7989_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of the main works by both Thomas Kuhn and Bertrand Russell?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7989_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7989_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7989_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7989_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7989_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7989_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7989_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7989_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7989_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7989_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7989_76.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents does not mention an influence of Bertrand Russell on Thomas Kuhn. The document mentions Kuhn's relationship with James B. Conant and the Cold War, but there is no mention of an intellectual influence from Bertrand Russell."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided documents do not contain any information about Thomas Kuhn being influenced by Bertrand Russell. While the texts discuss Thomas Kuhn's influence on science education and his theories, there is no mention of his influences from other philosophers or intellectuals like Bertrand Russell."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "There is no evidence provided in the context to support the assertion that Thomas Kuhn was influenced by Bertrand Russell. While it's possible that there could have been an influence, the information provided does not substantiate this claim.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}